Guide to the Max Ewing Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Other Papers, 1901-2003, undated; Series VI; 1.05; (3 boxes) + 1 portfolio
  - Unidentified head, sculpted in clay, undated
  - "From Pioneer to Fame and Back: The Selected Correspondence of Max Ewing" by Wallace K. Ewing, 2003 (Box Portfolio 33)
    Gift of Wallace K. Ewing, 2003
- Restricted Fragile, 1; (3 boxes)
  - Nitrate negatives for "Carnival of Venice" (Box 34)
  - "Speak-O-Phone personal phonograph" sound recordings (Box 35, Folder 250-251)
  - Unidentified head, sculpted in clay (Box 36)